txodds.com 2019-04-04

# Cookies & Privacy Policy | TXODDS

TXODDS Sport Betting Limited is committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to our website at http://txodds.net. Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us.

By registering or placing an order on this website, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this policy.

### INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT FROM YOU

When you visit, register or order products or services on https://txodds.net or https://txodds.com you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself including your name, contact details and credit or debit card information.

We may also collect information about your usage of our website as well as information about you from messages you post to the website and e-mails or letters you send to us.

To maintain customer service standards and to assist staff training, we may record and monitor incoming calls.

### USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

Your information will enable us to provide you with access to all parts of our website and to supply the goods or services you have requested. It will also enable us to bill you and to contact you where necessary concerning your orders. We will also use and analyse the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our business.

### **DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

The information you provide to us may be accessed by or given to third parties some of whom may be located outside the European Economic Area who act for us for the purposes set out in this policy or for other purposes approved by you. Those parties process information, fulfil and deliver orders, process credit card payments and provide support services on our behalf. We may also pass aggregate information on the usage of our website to third parties but this will not include information that can be used to identify you.

If our business enters into a joint venture with or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your information may be disclosed to our new business partners or owners.

Countries outside the European Economic Area do not always have strong data protection laws. However, we will always take steps to ensure that your information is used by third parties in accordance with this policy.

Unless required to do so by law, we will not otherwise share, sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us without your consent.

### **COOKIES**

Cookies are small amounts of information which we may store on your computer.

Unless you have indicated your objection when disclosing your details to us, our system will issue cookies to your computer when you log on to the site. Cookies make it easier for you to log on to and use the site during future visits. They also allow us to monitor website traffic and to personalise the content of the site for you. You may set up your computer to reject cookies by following the relevant instructions which can be found at www.aboutcookies.org. In that case, you may not be able to use certain features on our site which rely on storing cookies for providing correct information.

### SECURITY AND DATA RETENTION

We employ security measure to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. Your information will be retained for so long as it is required of us to keep that information to comply with out statutory or regulatory obligations. We may also keep your information for the purposes of contacting you for marketing purposes both during our relationship with you as well as afterwards if you have indicated by positively opting in to being contacted for these purposes.

### ACCESSING AND UPDATING

You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us at helpdesk@txodds.com.

Under the [General Data Protection Regulation](http://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/PDF/?uri=CELEX:32016R0679&from=EN) you have a number of important rights free of charge. In summary, those include rights to:

  1. fair processing of information and transparency over how we use your use personal information
  2. access to your personal information and to certain other supplementary information that this **PrivacyNotice** is already designed to address
  3. require us to correct any mistakes in your information which we hold
  4. require the erasure of personal information concerning you in certain situations
  5. receive the personal information concerning you which you have provided to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those data to a third party in certain situations
  6. object at any time to processing of personal information concerning you for direct marketing
  7. object to decisions being taken by automated means which produce legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affect you
  8. object in certain other situations to our continued processing of your personal information
  9. otherwise restrict our processing of your personal information in certain circumstances
  10. claim compensation for damages caused by our breach of any data protection laws

For further information on each of those rights, including the circumstances in which they apply, see the [Guidance from the UK Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) on individuals rights under the General Data Protection Regulation](http://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/).

If you would like to exercise any of those rights, please:

  1. email, call or write to our Data Protection Officer
  2. let us have enough information to identify you _(eg account number, user name, registration details)_ ,
  3. let us have proof of your identity and address (a copy of your driving license or passport and a recent utility or credit card bill), and
  4. let us know the information to which your request relates, including any account or reference numbers, if you have them

### KEEPING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE

We have appropriate security measures in place to prevent personal information from being accidentally lost, or used or accessed in an unauthorised way. We limit access to your personal information to those who have a genuine business need to know it. Those processing your information will do so only in an authorised manner and are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

We also have procedures in place to deal with any suspected data security breach. We will notify you and any applicable regulator of a suspected data security breach where we are legally required to do so.

** ** If you want detailed information from Get Safe Online on how to protect your information and your computers and devices against fraud, identity theft, viruses and many other online problems, please visit [www.getsafeonline.org](http://www.getsafeonline.org/). Get Safe Online is supported by HM Government and leading businesses.

### HOW TO COMPLAIN

We hope that we can resolve any query or concern you raise about our use of your information.

The [General Data Protection Regulation](http://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/PDF/?uri=CELEX:32016R0679&from=EN) also gives you right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the European Union (or European Economic Area) state where you work, normally live or where any alleged infringement of data protection laws occurred. The supervisory authority in the UK is the Information Commissioner who may be contacted at [https://ico.org.uk/concerns/](http://ico.org.uk/concerns/) or telephone: _0303 123 1113_.

### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Any changes to our privacy policy in the future will be posted to the website and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification.

### CONTACT

All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to dataprotection@txodds.com.
